(Adam:)Oh, if you're gonna
factor in a sense of humor,
(Adam:)then I should be
at the top of the list.
(Adam:)It should be me,
(Adam:)Keaton, Kilmer,
(Adam:)Lego, Bale,
(Adam:)and that pretty boy Clooney.
(Howard:)Really?
(Howard:)You're ahead of Bale?
(Howard:)The man who personified
the words,
(deep voice):
“I'm Batman.”
(Adam:)I never had to say I'm Batman.
(Adam:)I showed up.
(Adam:)People knew I was Batman.
(Adam:)Everywhere I went...
on the TV show,
(Adam:)mall openings...
(Adam:)Julie Newmar's bungalow.
(Leonard:)I'm sold... you're ahead of Bale.
(Adam:)There's another reason
I should be higher on the list.
(Adam:)All those other guys
(Adam:)had muscles built
into their costumes.
(Adam:)All I had in my Batsuit
(Adam:)was 100%, grade-A West.